bio-rad-antibodies.com 2017-03-21

# Privacy Policy | Bio-Rad (formerly AbD Serotec)

###  General

We want to protect the privacy of visitors to our Website and the privacy of our customers, collaborators, contacts and other individuals whose personal data we handle. Please read the following policy; it will help you to understand how we use personal data.

###  Who We Are

This policy explains how Bio-Rad AbD Serotec Ltd, whose registered office is at Endeavour House, Langford Business Park, Langford Lane, Kidlington, Oxfordshire, UK, registered number 1604642, VAT number 336458245 uses personal data.

###  Consent To Our Use Of Your Personal Data

**Whenever you give us personal data, you are consenting to its collection and use in accordance with this privacy policy, including our use of cookies as explained below.**

###  What Personal Data Do We Collect?

When you visit our Website we log your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on our website. We use this to receive and send information from and to you over the internet and to monitor your use of our website.

When you contact us about the supply of any of our goods or services, make an inquiry, order products or services from us or ask us for information, you will be asked to provide some personal data (such as your name, business or billing address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit or debit card number).

We may use information about you from credit reference agencies and fraud prevention agencies.

We also automatically collect data about visitors to our Website (for example on browsing patterns) by using Cookies. These data allow us to recognize you and your preferred settings and avoid you having to re-enter information when you visit this Website in future. (See below for more information on Cookies.)

###  Cookies

A Cookie is a small piece of data or message that is sent from a Web server to your browser and is stored on your hard drive. It is used to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information.

A Cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read Cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system.

For further information visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

You can reset your browser to refuse Cookies or to alert you to when a Cookie is being sent. For information about this look in your browser’s ‘help’ facility. The above Websites also tell you how to remove Cookies from your browser.

If you choose not to accept our Cookies, some of the features of our Website may not work as well as we intend.

We use Cookies for the purposes of system administration of our Website, to give us information about the number of visitors to different parts of our Website, and to enhance your visit to our Website.

###  How Do We Use Personal Data?

We use your personal data to:

  * supply goods, services and information to you or your organization
  * manage your or your organization’s account
  * to let you know about other goods and services in which you may be interested
  * to inform you about changes and improvements to our Website
  * for direct marketing purposes (but you may opt out of this) and
  * if you agree, to email you about products and services in which you may be interested

We may also use your personal data to:

  * monitor the use of our Website and personalize your visits to that Website
  * to record traffic flows to our Website
  * to carry out research about our visitors’ and customers’ demographics, interests and behavior so that we can better understand our visitors, customers and potential customers.

When you give us personal data, those data may be sent electronically to servers anywhere in the world and may be used, stored and processed anywhere in the world, including countries outside the European Economic Area. **(Bear in mind that many countries outside the EEA do not adequately protect your rights as a data subject.)**

###  To Whom Might We Disclose Personal Data?

We may disclose your personal data to affiliate companies of Bio-Rad for direct marketing purposes.

We may disclose your personal data in order to fulfill your requests for goods, services and information, or to validate any payment details you give to us. Some of these people may be located outside the European Economic Area.

We may also provide your personal data to anyone who buys our business or business assets.

Except as set out above, we will not disclose your personal data unless we are obliged to do so or allowed to do so by law, or where we need to do so in order to run our business (for instance where we outsource services or other people who process data for us).

###  Direct Marketing

We may contact you by e-mail to market our goods and services. You have the right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you wish to do that, you can unsubscribe anytime by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the top of all our email communications.

Alternatively, please contact: [antibody_ebusiness@bio-rad.com](mailto:antibody_ebusiness@bio-rad.com) or +44 (0)1865 852 700, or you can write to us at Bio-Rad AbD Serotec Ltd, Endeavour House, Langford Business Park, Langford Lane, Kidlington, Oxfordshire, OX5 1GE, UK.

###  Access To Your Personal Data and Correcting It

You have the right to request a copy of the personal data which we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal data, please contact: [antibody_ebusiness@bio-rad.com](mailto:antibody_ebusiness@bio-rad.com), or +44 (0) 1865 852 700, or alternatively you should write to us at Bio-Rad AbD Serotec Ltd, Endeavour House, Langford Business Park, Langford Lane, Kidlington, Oxfordshire, OX5 1GE, UK.

We would like to keep your personal data accurate and up to date. If you become aware of any errors or inaccuracies please let us know by contacting: [antibody_ebusiness@bio-rad.com](mailto:antibody_ebusiness@bio-rad.com) or +44 (0) 1865 852 700, or alternatively you may write to us at Bio-Rad AbD Serotec Ltd, Endeavour House, Langford Business Park, Langford Lane, Kidlington, Oxfordshire, OX5 1GE, UK.

###  Links To Other Websites

Our Website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this Website. When you link to other websites you should read their privacy policies.

###  Security

When we process or use personal data, we take steps to ensure that it is treated securely and in accordance with our privacy policy.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet or any other network can be guaranteed as 100% secure, but we take appropriate steps to try to protect the security of your personal data.

###  Changes To This Privacy Policy

We keep this privacy policy under regular review and we may change it from time to time. Any updates will appear on this webpage. Please check it each time you visit this Website or provide us with any personal data.

We last updated this privacy policy on 22nd May, 2013.

###  How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or any personal data which we hold about you, please contact: [antibody_ebusiness@bio-rad.com](mailto:antibody_ebusiness@bio-rad.com) or +44 (0)1865 852 700, or alternatively you can write to us at Bio-Rad AbD Serotec Ltd, Endeavour House, Langford Business Park, Langford Lane, Kidlington, Oxfordshire, OX5 1GE, UK.
